{
    "user_name": "lschuth",
    "session_complete_time": "2018-12-03 09:39:45.471980",
    "session_pk": 8,
    "session_size": 6,
    "block_size": 6,
    "policy_id": 3,
    "block_data": [
        {
            "block_id": 28,
            "qanda_data": [
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 165,
                    "question_pk": 568,
                    "question": "Words swim on the page for me; it's difficult to see them, let alone read them.",
                    "chunk": "see them, let alone read them",
                    "chunk_translation": "sehe sie, geschweige denn, sie zu lesen",
                    "answer": "see them let alone read them",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 166,
                    "question_pk": 89,
                    "question": "When she did get there, the midwife was astounded because I was so big.",
                    "chunk": "she did get there",
                    "chunk_translation": "Sie ist dort angekommen",
                    "answer": "she got there",
                    "answer_correct": false,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 167,
                    "question_pk": 117,
                    "question": "But the real achievement is not what I've done; it's how long I've lived.",
                    "chunk": "how long I've lived",
                    "chunk_translation": "Wie lange lebe ich schon",
                    "answer": "how long I've lived",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 168,
                    "question_pk": 189,
                    "question": "Before the operation, I posted a video of him dancing on the Ed Sullivan Show, and thought, In one year, I'll be doing this.",
                    "chunk": "thought, In one year, I'll be doing this",
                    "chunk_translation": "dachte, In einem Jahr werde ich das tun",
                    "answer": "I thought in one year I'll be doing this",
                    "answer_correct": false,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 169,
                    "question_pk": 1153,
                    "question": "Once I went to college and lived alone, this became a bigger problem; I was increasingly afraid of going to sleep at night.",
                    "chunk": "to sleep at night",
                    "chunk_translation": "nachts schlafen",
                    "answer": "to sleep at night",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 170,
                    "question_pk": 471,
                    "question": "Sebastian began to cry: he could see I was in pain.",
                    "chunk": "he could see I was in pain",
                    "chunk_translation": "Er konnte sehen, dass ich Schmerzen hatte",
                    "answer": "He could see that I was in pain",
                    "answer_correct": false,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "block_id": 29,
            "qanda_data": [
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 177,
                    "question_pk": 590,
                    "question": "When I started secondary school, a teacher made me stand on a chair and read.",
                    "chunk": "I started secondary school",
                    "chunk_translation": "Ich habe die Sekundarschule begonnen",
                    "answer": "I started secondary school",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "exploit"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 178,
                    "question_pk": 1023,
                    "question": "When I opened my eyes, I was upside down.",
                    "chunk": "I opened my eyes",
                    "chunk_translation": "Ich \u00f6ffnete meine Augen",
                    "answer": "I opened my eyes",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "exploit"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 179,
                    "question_pk": 995,
                    "question": "Ryan and I had been zip lining before, so when we saw signs for an ecopark boasting 11 lines in the middle of the jungle, we thought, Let's go for it.",
                    "chunk": "in the middle of the jungle",
                    "chunk_translation": "mitten im Dschungel",
                    "answer": "in the middle of the the jungle",
                    "answer_correct": false,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 180,
                    "question_pk": 1084,
                    "question": "I didn't want surgery, though, as nothing was broken.",
                    "chunk": "want surgery, though, as nothing was broken",
                    "chunk_translation": "Ich m\u00f6chte aber operiert werden, da nichts kaputt war",
                    "answer": "want a surgery as nothing broke though",
                    "answer_correct": false,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 181,
                    "question_pk": 954,
                    "question": "Then, just as we started to make the first cut, my colleague punched in the correct code.",
                    "chunk": "in the correct code",
                    "chunk_translation": "im richtigen Code",
                    "answer": "in the correct code",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 182,
                    "question_pk": 352,
                    "question": "It was really quite peaceful: I saw a forest either side of me, and I was just walking into it.",
                    "chunk": "It was really quite peaceful",
                    "chunk_translation": "Es war wirklich sehr friedlich",
                    "answer": "It was really quite peaceful",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "block_id": 30,
            "qanda_data": [
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 171,
                    "question_pk": 697,
                    "question": "From afar, it looked as if it was dead, but then I saw a leg move.",
                    "chunk": "then I saw a leg move",
                    "chunk_translation": "dann sah ich eine Beinbewegung",
                    "answer": null,
                    "answer_correct": null,
                    "qanda_type": "exploit"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 172,
                    "question_pk": 28,
                    "question": "The rollercoaster ride went on for three or four minutes, and I enjoyed every second.",
                    "chunk": "went on for three or four minutes",
                    "chunk_translation": "ging f\u00fcr drei oder vier Minuten weiter",
                    "answer": null,
                    "answer_correct": null,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 173,
                    "question_pk": 13,
                    "question": "I didn't choose to go on that  it was a bit too gentle.",
                    "chunk": "was a bit too gentle",
                    "chunk_translation": "war ein bisschen zu sanft",
                    "answer": null,
                    "answer_correct": null,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 174,
                    "question_pk": 793,
                    "question": "When we got home, I put the coat straight in a hot wash.",
                    "chunk": "put the coat straight in a hot wash",
                    "chunk_translation": "Legen Sie den Mantel gerade in eine hei\u00dfe W\u00e4sche",
                    "answer": null,
                    "answer_correct": null,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 175,
                    "question_pk": 929,
                    "question": "While we were doing this, the boy's mother remembered that her brother had once opened the safe, so when the codes we had didn't work, she called him.",
                    "chunk": "While we were doing this",
                    "chunk_translation": "W\u00e4hrend wir das machten",
                    "answer": null,
                    "answer_correct": null,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 176,
                    "question_pk": 1110,
                    "question": "The company denied that the line had become detached or broken, but the fact that I ended up upside down in a tree means something went very wrong.",
                    "chunk": "means something went very wrong",
                    "chunk_translation": "bedeutet, dass etwas sehr falsch gelaufen ist",
                    "answer": null,
                    "answer_correct": null,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "block_id": 31,
            "qanda_data": [
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 183,
                    "question_pk": 390,
                    "question": "He had left that message while I was buried.",
                    "chunk": "left that message while I was buried",
                    "chunk_translation": "verlie\u00df diese Nachricht, w\u00e4hrend ich begraben wurde",
                    "answer": "left that message while I was buried",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "exploit"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 184,
                    "question_pk": 833,
                    "question": "It's what safes are designed for  not to be opened.",
                    "chunk": "designed for  not to be opened",
                    "chunk_translation": "entworfen, um nicht ge\u00f6ffnet zu werden",
                    "answer": "designed for not to be opened ",
                    "answer_correct": false,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 185,
                    "question_pk": 1120,
                    "question": "Do your research, but don't live your life in fear.",
                    "chunk": "live your life in fear",
                    "chunk_translation": "Lebe dein Leben in Angst",
                    "answer": "live your life in fear",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 186,
                    "question_pk": 1204,
                    "question": "The first day I woke up after closing the loop, I was blown away by how much better I felt.",
                    "chunk": "The first day ",
                    "chunk_translation": "Der erste Tag",
                    "answer": "The first day",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 187,
                    "question_pk": 438,
                    "question": "I was having contractions the whole time and Richard was tracking the car  it was frustrating, to say the least.",
                    "chunk": "the car  ",
                    "chunk_translation": "das Auto",
                    "answer": "the car",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 188,
                    "question_pk": 96,
                    "question": "I was married, for a very long time, to the best wife in the world and she died very suddenly of a stroke when she was 68.",
                    "chunk": "for a very long time",
                    "chunk_translation": "f\u00fcr eine sehr lange Zeit",
                    "answer": "for a very long time",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "block_id": 32,
            "qanda_data": [
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 189,
                    "question_pk": 367,
                    "question": "When they pulled me out, they couldn't find a pulse and I wasn't breathing, so Gordon started giving me CPR.",
                    "chunk": "couldn't find a pulse ",
                    "chunk_translation": "konnte keinen Puls finden",
                    "answer": "couldn't find a pulse",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 190,
                    "question_pk": 389,
                    "question": "I had a voicemail from one of the ski instructors saying: Hey, just to let you know it's a really high avalanche risk today, there have been three people buried in avalanches in different areas already, so just be very careful.",
                    "chunk": "the ski instructors ",
                    "chunk_translation": "die Skilehrer",
                    "answer": "the ski instructors",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 191,
                    "question_pk": 732,
                    "question": "One vital bit of information was that if the head is out and the two front hooves are tucked under the chin, that's the correct birthing position.",
                    "chunk": "One vital bit of information ",
                    "chunk_translation": "Ein wichtiges St\u00fcck Information",
                    "answer": "One vital bit of information",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 192,
                    "question_pk": 903,
                    "question": "Next, we had to work out the combination: blindly opening the safe by force might have hurt or suffocated the boy.",
                    "chunk": "work out the combination",
                    "chunk_translation": "die Kombination ausarbeiten",
                    "answer": "work out the combination",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 193,
                    "question_pk": 216,
                    "question": "I used videos to track my progress.",
                    "chunk": "used videos to track my progress",
                    "chunk_translation": "benutzte Videos, um meine Fortschritte zu verfolgen",
                    "answer": "use videos to track my progress",
                    "answer_correct": false,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 194,
                    "question_pk": 726,
                    "question": "But I felt we had to do something.",
                    "chunk": "felt we had to do something",
                    "chunk_translation": "Ich f\u00fchlte, dass wir etwas tun mussten",
                    "answer": "felt that we had to do something",
                    "answer_correct": false,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "block_id": 33,
            "qanda_data": [
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 195,
                    "question_pk": 498,
                    "question": "About 10 minutes after the birth, while I was still in the medical centre and we were waiting for the ambulance, my husband scrubbed down the taxi.",
                    "chunk": "in the medical centre ",
                    "chunk_translation": "im medizinischen Zentrum",
                    "answer": "in the medical centre",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 196,
                    "question_pk": 45,
                    "question": "I have it on the wall in my living room, with another one that I got a year earlier for being the oldest person in the world to get their first tattoo.",
                    "chunk": "in the world to get their first tattoo",
                    "chunk_translation": "in der Welt, um ihr erstes Tattoo zu bekommen",
                    "answer": "in the world to get their first tattoo",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 197,
                    "question_pk": 226,
                    "question": "There is a different technique; with a real foot you've got a heel and toe, and you can make different sounds and rhythms.",
                    "chunk": "a real foot ",
                    "chunk_translation": "ein echter Fu\u00df",
                    "answer": "a real foot",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 198,
                    "question_pk": 155,
                    "question": "It was during a production in 2009 at university, where I was studying musical theatre, that I started to feel pain in my right leg.",
                    "chunk": "to feel pain in my right leg",
                    "chunk_translation": "Schmerz in meinem rechten Bein sp\u00fcren",
                    "answer": "to feel pain my right leg",
                    "answer_correct": false,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 199,
                    "question_pk": 653,
                    "question": "I applied to do a degree, biological medicine and health sciences, at the Open University.",
                    "chunk": "at the Open University",
                    "chunk_translation": "an der offenen Universit\u00e4t",
                    "answer": "at the open university",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 200,
                    "question_pk": 780,
                    "question": "She slowly went towards the lamb and eventually picked up the scent.",
                    "chunk": "towards the lamb ",
                    "chunk_translation": "auf das Lamm zu",
                    "answer": "towards the lamb",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}